你们这时候得动点想象力 好吗
Now, you gotta use your imagination here, okay?
不要只看表面的东西
Don't judge a book by its cover.
这里曾是西屋家电制造厂
This used to be Westinghouse Appliance Manufacturing.
这幢楼占地十四英亩
This sits on a 14-acre lot.
单是这层就有两万平方英尺
This floor alone, 20, 000 square feet.
跟我说说俄亥俄州吧 先生们
Tell me about Ohio, gentlemen.
这儿产出过最多的宇航员和最多的总统
Most astronauts and most presidents.
真的吗
Really?
我认为到目前为止
I think 25 astronauts.
已经有25位宇航员和8位总统了
and eight presidents so far.
张小姐
Ms. Zhang, please.
我不认为你的爸爸会同意的
I don't think your father would agree.
不不 我喜欢这儿 鲍
No, no. I like it here, Bao.
这两幢楼我都喜欢
I like both buildings.
汽车制造商 钢铁厂 电器厂
Car manufacturers, steel mills, electrical appliances.
这里的人们失去了一切
People here lost it all.
他们是真的想找到工作
They really wanna work.
你从他们眼里就能看出来
You can see it in their eyes.
我觉得这是一项很好的提议
I think this is a really good move.
- 稍等 达雅 - 爸爸 请相信我
- Hold on, Daya. - Dad, please trust me.
达雅 等等 等等
Daya, hold on, hold on.
沙特阿拉伯人知道我们把这个盖在船上
The royal family knows we built this in the hull of a ship.
王子问我们可不可以把它盖在沙子底下
They asked if we could build one under the desert.
120亿 先付一半
Twelve billion. Half in advance.
宝贝 在中国境外开设工厂
Honey, opening plants outside of China.
可能达不到国内这样的水平
may not play so well here.
但是给美国带来就业机会
But bringing jobs into America.
能提升我们的国际知名度
will help our worldwide brand.
我觉得这是一项很好的提议
I think it would be a good move.
双方共赢 我真的很想促成这件事
Both sides win. I really want to do this.
好吗
Okay?
那么就是25位宇航员和8位总统吗
So, 25 astronauts and eight presidents?
到目前为止
So far.
中国潮要来登陆曼斯菲尔德了
China's coming to Mansfield.
太棒了 谢谢
Fantastic! Thank you.
我们很高兴张氏科技
We are so glad Zhang Innovations.
正在考虑对曼斯菲尔德投资
is considering Mansfield for investment,
我们会倾其所能地促成这笔交易
and we are gonna do whatever it takes to get that deal done for you.
谢谢你 市长先生
Thank you, Mr. Mayor.
我们对目前的现状非常满意
We were very pleased with everything that we saw.
我们肯定会再联系的
We'll definitely be in touch.
太好了 我期待着你的回电
Fantastic. I look forward to your call.
- 一路顺风 - 谢谢
- And safe travels. - Thank you.
张小姐 这边
This way, Ms. Zhang.
你的贴身保镖一刻不离 紧盯着你啊
Your bodyguard never relaxes. He doesn't take his eyes off you.
我知道
I know.
他很尽职
He is very thorough.
他接替了罗沈 已经很好了
But it is difficult to fill the shoes of Shen.
你父亲讨厌罗沈
Your father hated Shen.
沈根本没错 他只是喜欢我
Shen did nothing wrong but love me.
（雷·布雷斯林）
在七楼有个漂亮的接待员
Seventh floor, there's a pretty receptionist.
（加利福尼亚州 洛杉矶）
如果你能撩上她
If you can charm your way through her,
你就可以完全避开安保
you can avoid security altogether.
阿比盖尔 我在想你之前说的
You know Abigail, I was thinking about what you were saying.
我们要一起同居的事情
about us moving in together.
我觉得想法挺好 不过还有一个小问题
You know, I think it's a pretty good idea, except for one small thing.
叫作 打鼾
I think it's called "snoring."
什么啊 乱讲 我可不打鼾
What? Get out of here! I don't snore.
如果不是你 我就不知道是谁打的鼾了
If it ain't you, I don't know who it is.
不过我也可以塞点东西 弄个木塞之类的
But I could put something, maybe a cork or something,
可能会让你稍微消停点
and it'll keep you a little more quiet.
好了 雷 我们谈正事吧
All right, Ray, we gotta focus.
我们得拿到那个磁盘 并确保要
We need to get that disk and make sure our names aren't tied.
跟你前搭档的黑狱活动撇清关系
to your ex-partner's black site activity,
我们才能可以睡个好觉
and we sleep better.
睡个好觉 我能美美地醒来
And when I sleep better, I wake up happy,
而我心情美滋滋的时候
and when I'm sweet,
你就可以在床上享受端来的早餐
and you'll get breakfast in bed.
好的 阿比盖尔 就这么说定了
All right, Abigail, that's a deal.
我爱你 雷
I love you, Ray.
我也爱你
I love you too.
请问周先生在吗
Mr. Chow, please.
我可以问一下你找他有什么事吗
May I tell him what this is regarding?
- 不行 - 不行吗
- No. - No?
- 这是个惊喜 - 他并不喜欢惊喜
- It's a surprise. - He's not big on surprises.
- 你叫什么 - 朋友
Your name? Friend.
来了一位叫朋友的先生
Mr. Friend is here.
是的 朋友先生
Yes, Mr. Friend.
中国人 带着公文包和雨伞
Chinese, with a briefcase and an umbrella.
不 先生 没在下雨
No, sir, not raining. Mm-hmm.
他马上就来 朋友先生
Be right with you, Mr. Friend.
谢谢
Thank you.
先生
Sir?
惊喜吧
Surprise.
我需要那个
I want that.
- 我也需要它 - 把磁盘给我
- I want it too. - Give me the disk.
你不会开枪的 雷·布雷斯林
You're not gonna shoot me, Ray Breslin.
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
- 罗沈 - 我们来看看磁盘里的东西
- Shen Lo. - We're gonna see what's on that disk.
等我满意了 就归你了
And if I'm satisfied, then you can have it.
走吧
Walk.
（俄亥俄州 曼斯菲尔德）
很明显 这些人都是专业的
Obviously, these guys were professionals.
我觉得我们能在这点上达成一致
I think we can agree on that.
他们掌握了你们的时间表
They knew your timetable.
他们掌握了你们的行踪
They knew where you were gonna be.
他们知道她什么时候离开
They knew when she was leaving.
他们知道什么时候在机库蹲守
They knew when to be at the hangar.
我实话跟你说 我们毫无线索
I'm gonna be honest with you. We've got nothing.
这是你的护卫任务
This was your detail.
是你在负责她的安全
You were responsible for her.
听着 就像我之前说的 我们进了城
Look, as I told him, we came into town…
是啊 是啊 是啊 我们都听到了
Yeah, yeah, yeah, we've heard all that.
你们进了城 在四处物色房地产
You're in town, you're looking at real estate.
我说的就是实话
I'm telling you the truth.
有没有注意到什么不一样的地方
Was there anything different?
有什么你觉得突出的迹象
Was there something that stood out to you?
这一切都说不通
None of this is making sense.
好吧 想一想 从头开始想
All right, just think about it, from the beginning.
你最初看到的是什么
What was the first thing you saw?
你记得的第一件事是什么
What's the first thing you remember?
你能告诉我们些什么
What can you tell us?
肯定有你能告诉我们的事情
There's gotta be something you can tell us,
一些发生了的事情
something that happened.
你是唯一幸存的人
You're the only person that's alive.
我总不能去问这些死人
I certainly can't ask them.
是你在负责她的安全
You were responsible for her.
告诉我
Tell me.
谁干的
Who took her?
- 我不知道 - 你怎么会不知道
- I don't know. - You have to know.
我真的不知道
I don't.
你发誓用生命保护她的安全
You are supposed to protect my daughter with your life.
为什么她被绑架了 而你还在这
If you did your job right, you'd be dead.
我尽力了 我被打晕了
I tried. I was knocked out.
别激动 带他离开这
Hey, hey! Whoa! Get him outta here!
- 够了 够了 - 她人呢 她人呢
- That's enough, that's enough! - Where is she? Where is she?
- 把他带出去 把他带出去 - 说啊
- Get him outta here! Get him outta here! - Tell me!
来吧 我们走 我们走吧
Come on, let's go. Let's go.
把你的手拿开 别碰我
Take your hands off me! Don't touch me!
- 坐下吧 我还没审完你呢 - 走吧
- Have a seat. I'm not done with you. - Let's go.
别碰我
Don't touch me!
如果那个磁盘没问题 你就可以走了
If that disk is clear, you can be on your way.
我难道应该还要谢谢你放我走吗
Am I supposed to say thank you?
这是罗沈
This is Shen Lo.
- 你好 很高兴见到你 - 嗨
- Hello. Very nice to meet you. - Hi.
一切都准备好了
Everything's set.
哈什和阿比盖尔在等你们
Hush and Abigail are waiting.
好的
Okay.
雷 你有空谈谈吗
Ray, have you got a second?
我知道你要说什么
I know what you're gonna say.
我准备好要加入实战行动了
I'm ready to get up from behind this desk.
只要你能随便给我个机会
if you wanna accidentally give me a chance.
我会考虑的
I'll think about it.
- 一切都好吗 - 没问题
- All good? - Clear.
没什么能把你和他联系起来
Nothing to tie you to him.
你是说张吗
You mean Zhang?
你想找什么
What are you looking for?
- 我知道你和张有生意来往 - 是吗
- I know you were in business with Zhang. - Do you?
你的搭档曾经有 张投资了你的公司
Your partner was. Zhang financed your company.
- 我们与此无关 - 莱斯特有关
- We had nothing to do with that. - Lester did.
那你是怎么知道的
And how do you know that?
我在张手下当过安保主管
I worked for him. Head of security for Zhang.
让我给你捋一捋
Let me set you straight.
都是莱斯特跟他谈的生意 不是我
Lester did the business, not me.
也许是时候该我插上一句
Maybe it's time for me to interject into the conversation.
他们愿意出双倍的标准费用
that they have offered double your standard fee.
那就是五百万 雷
That's five mil, Ray.
- 所以你喜欢这笔生意吗 - 我很喜欢
- So you like this? - Yes, I like it very much.
从报酬方面来看 我喜欢这笔生意
From a financial standpoint, I like it.
你为什么现在要追查张总
Why are you going after Zhang now?
这些黑狱背后的技术都是由张氏开发的
All the technology behind all of these black site prisons is Zhang's.
但你已经知道了 不是吗
But you know that already, don't you?
你想说什么
What's your point?
依我看来
My point.
看看这些数据
Look at the data.
张的技术让他在监禁和折磨
Zhang's technology has made him billions.
成千上万的人上赚了数十亿
on imprisoning and torturing thousands of people.
张氏科技的创新之处就在于洗钱方式
Zhang Innovations is how he cleans that money.
我要把他打垮 这是私人恩怨
I'm gonna bring him down. It's personal.
你想找张算账 你自己解决
You wanna go after Zhang, do it yourself.
我们对背后的情况一无所知
We had no idea what was going on behind our backs.
已经了结了 事已至此 到此为止
It's dead, and it's history. That's it.
我们现在撇清关系了
We're clean now.
好吧 那么莱斯特·克拉克现在在哪儿
All right, so where is Lester Clark now?
很久没见他了
Haven't seen him for a long time.
但我听说
But I heard…
他去长途旅行了
he went on a long cruise…
就再也没有回来
and never came back.
该睡觉了 混蛋
Sleepy time, motherfucker.
操
Fuck!
不 不 不 不 别 快点
No, no, no, no! Come on, come on.
操
Fuck!
雷
Ray!
打扰了 雷
Excuse me, Ray.
前台有个人
There's a man up front.
他说是通过国际刑警联系到我们的
He said he found us through an Interpol contact.
说他有东西你得看看
Claims he has something you need to see.
好吧 把他带进来吧
All right, just bring him in.
有什么能帮到你
Can I help you?
我叫鲍勇 我找雷·布雷斯林
My name is Bao Yung. I'm looking for Ray Breslin.
在下就是
Right here.
这是给你的
This is for you.
善有善报 恶有恶报
What goes around, comes around.
雷·布雷斯林 你看到这个的时候
Ray Breslin, by the time you see this,
我已经绑架了张达雅
I'll have Daya Zhang,
而且我很快就会来找你了
and I'll be coming for you.
达雅
Daya.
- 那是 - 是的
- Is that… - Yeah.
- 是谁 - 小莱斯特·克拉克
- Who is it? - Lester Clark Jr.
我前合伙人的儿子
My ex-partner's son.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是张氏科技的安全主管
I was head of security at Zhang Innovations.
张达雅被绑架了
Daya Zhang was kidnapped.
那你现在还站这儿干嘛不去找她
Why are you here instead of looking for her?
不是我的错
It's not my fault.
不是你的错是谁的错
If it's not your fault, whose fault is it?
别吵了
Come on.
集中注意力
Focus.
- 这是什么地方 - 哈什 放大点
- Where's this place? - Hush, go closer.
墙上
On the wall.
那个 那幅画 《狮窝中的丹尼尔》
That. That picture."Daniel in the Lions' Den."
- 囚犯的守护神 - 是的
- The patron saint of prisoners. - Right.
这是监狱教堂
That's a prison chapel.
- 东正教 也许 - 是的
- Eastern Orthodox, maybe? - Yeah.
但写的是俄语
But the writing's in Russian.
是的 可能是东方集团
Yeah, it's probably Eastern Bloc.
- 朱勒 去找特伦特 - 现在去
- Jules, get Trent. - On it.
（爱沙尼亚 塔林）
（雷 来电）
- 怎么了 雷 - 嘿 我的朋友
- What's up, Ray? - Hey, my friend.
- 你收到录像了吗 - 收到了
- Did you get the video? - Yeah.
收到了 怎么了
Yeah, I did. What's going down?
我前搭档的孩子走上不归路了
My ex-partner's kid went off the rails.
是啊 很明显
Yeah, obviously.
你觉得这个地方是哪里
Where do you think this place is?
看起来很眼熟
Definitely looks familiar.
多眼悉
How familiar?
这种地方所剩不多了
Not many of these places left.
好的 所以你觉得是哪儿
All right, so what's your call?
恶魔车站
Devil's Station.
不是个好地方 雷
Bad place, Ray.
离白俄罗斯约320公里
About 200 miles outside of Belarus.
好了 瘦子先生 你能帮忙吗
Okay, Mr. Skinny, can you help me out on this?
免费的吗 我只是开玩笑
For free? I'm just kidding.
- 我来负责交通 - 好的
- I'll take care of the transportation. - All right.
我们明天就去 欠你个人情
We'll be there tomorrow. I owe you.
是啊 哪次不是
Yeah, what's new?
你确定你不想呆在基地吗
You sure you don't wanna sit this one out?
不可能 让你独享所有的乐趣吗
No way. Let you have all the fun?
我们这里有哈什了
We got Hush back here.
我去收拾行李 拿好装备
I'll go pack our bags, get the gear,
一小时后回来
be back in an hour.
好的
You got it.
我一起去
I'm coming along.
当你说私人恩怨的时候 有多私人
When you said personal, how personal?
我跟达雅很亲近 我必须去
I was very close to Daya. I have to go.
那我们走吧 神秘人
Let's go, mystery man.
你 别在这儿搞破坏
And you, don't break anything.
（恶魔车站 拉脱维亚 德尔凡尼斯基）
我父亲可以为我们所有人买单
My father can pay for all of us.
安静
Quiet.
不许说话
No talking!
你想要什么
What do you want?
拜托 请不要这样做 好吗
Please. Please don't do this. Okay?
我们可以好好商量商量
We can work something out.
拜托 拜托
Please, please.
我们不是禽兽
We're not animals.
我们有规矩
We have rules.
如果有人们老是不守规矩
What's the point of having rules if.
那设规矩的意义又何在呢
people are gonna break 'em?
等等
Wait.
这是你的朋友吗
This your friend?
请不要伤害他 好吗
Just please don't hurt him, okay?
不会再发生了
L-lt won't happen again.
我 我保证
I-I promise.
我没有伤害他
I didn't hurt him.
- 是你干的 - 什么
- You did. - What?
不
No.
- 继续走吧 - 好了 走 快点
- Continue. - All right, go! Come on!
走
Go!
你是张氏科技的安保主管
You were head of security for Zhang Innovations.
对
Yes.
曾经是国际刑警 对吧
And you were with Interpol, yes?
对
Yes.
你怎么能让这种事情发生
How could you let this happen?
如果可以的话 我宁愿为她付出生命
I would've given my life to save her if I could have.
现在说这些还有什么用啊
It's too late to say that.
格洛克34
Glock.34,
9毫米长管型
nine millimeter, long slide.
好枪
Fancy.
达雅被带走的时候
And when they took Daya,
你这把枪到底在干嘛
where was your fancy gun then?
你让她失望了
You failed her.
我知道
I know.
- 喂 - 我来了 抱歉花了点时间
- Hey there. - I'm here. Sorry it took a little longer.
别担心 我也一堆事要做
Don't worry about it. I got tons of stuff to do here.
好吧 飞机在待命了 是个长途飞行
All right, plane's waiting. It's gonna be a long flight.
我们可以在床上吃早餐
We can have breakfast in bed.
听起来不错 阿比盖尔
Sounds good, Abigail.
艾比
Abby?
Abby!
- 艾比 - 雷
- Abby! - Ray!
去你妈的 雷
Fuck you! Ray!
艾比
Abby?
Abby!
操
Fuck.
该死
Damn it!
艾比
Abby!
他为什么还没打电话
Why hasn't he called yet?
这种情况发展捉摸不定
These things can go different ways.
那是什么意思
What does that mean?
你确定你没有敌人吗
Are you sure you don't have any enemies?
我在中国拥有第一的科技公司
I have the number one tech company in China.
中国13亿人都在用我的手机
There are 1.3 billion people in China, and everyone uses my phone.
我当然有敌人啊
Yes, I have enemies.
你不认为你应该从克利夫兰带些援助来吗
Don't you think you should bring some assistance here from Cleveland.
或是芝加哥
or Chicago?
你就想不出一个想伤害你女儿的人吗
There's no one you can think of that would want to harm your daughter?
让它响两声再接
Let it ring twice.
- 你好 - 张
- Hello? - Zhang.
你想要什么
What do you want?
加密了
Encrypted.
你本可以帮助我父亲的
You could've helped my father.
他把你的变态技术装在他所有的黑狱里
He put your sick technology in every one of his black site prisons,
而你却不必因此脏手
and you kept your hands clean.
现在 一切结束后 我会夺走你的金钱
Now, when this is done, I'm gonna take your money,
夺走你的技术 我要击垮你
I'm gonna take your technology, and I'm gonna break you.
原来我想要5亿美元
Before, I wanted $500 million.
现在我要7亿美元了 而且还会继续涨
Now I want $700 million, and it's going up.
看着
Watch.
这就是我们行动的资金来源
This is what funds our operation.
国家和公司供着
Paid by countries and corporations.
他们就不用处理那些脏到极致的事
to take the worst of the worst off their hands.
我已经杀了他们 但支票还在继续来
Now, I'd kill 'em, but the checks keep on coming.
杀人犯
Murderers.
连环强奸犯
Serial rapists.
恐怖分子 黑客 毒贩
Terrorists, hackers, narcos.
地球上的人渣
The scum of the earth.
世界上到处都有像你父亲一样的人渣
The world is full of scum like your father.
但你也清楚这点 对吧
But you know that, right?
锁起来
Lock 'em up!
我喜欢那声儿
I love that sound.
- 你来干嘛 - 我要对她负责任
- What are you doing? - She was my responsibility.
来吧 我们得走了
Come on. We gotta go.
这是一把1896年制造的电椅
It's an electric chair that was built in 1896.
实心橡木
It's, uh, solid oak.
如苹果派一样 典型美式的东西
It's as American as apple pie.
315人死在这张椅子上 包括三名妇女
Three hundred and 15 people died in that chair, including three women.
他们以前常常拿像这样的罩子
They used to, uh… They used to put a hood like this over the.
罩住囚犯的头
inmate's head,
但首先 他们会用棉花和胶带贴住眼睛
but first they would put cotton and tape over their eyes.
这样他们被电时 不会从里面往外乱溅
so they didn't pop out when they fried 'em from the inside.
你知道我是谁吗
You know who I am?
我父亲创立了你的公司
My father built your company.
然后雷·布雷斯林夺权 把他挤了出去
Ray Breslin took over, pushed him out.
不是这样的
That's not true.
胡说
Bullshit.
我和曾经发生的事无关
I had nothing to do with what happened.
是啊
Yeah.
是的 但你在场
Yeah, but you were there.
所以你算参与其中
So you're part of it.
（莫济里市 白俄罗斯）
给你
There you go.
没有你这事可成不了 伙计
Couldn't do this without you, man.
艾比的事我很抱歉 我们会解决的
I'm sorry about Abby. We'll set it straight.
是啊
Yeah.
这位是罗沈
This is Shen Lo.
失陪
Excuse me.
他话少
He doesn't have a lot to say.
- 你认识朱勒的 - 朱勒
- You know Jules. - Hey, Jules.
还有鲍勇
And Bao Yung.
- 安保人员吗 - 对
- Security? - Mm-hmm.
我以前弄丢过保护目标
I've lost an asset before.
- 真的吗 - 不
- Really? - No.
从来没有
Never.
- 这不好笑 - 当然好笑
- That's not funny. - Sure it is.
张先生
Mr. Zhang.
罗沈
Shen Lo.
你知道我的事情 对吧
You know about my situation?
我知道达雅被人绑架了
I know that Daya was kidnapped.
我可以救她
I can save her.
沈 沈
Shen. Shen!
如果你想让她活着回来的话 你就得听我的
If you want her alive, do what I say.
罗沈
Shen Lo.
我都是为了她
I only wanted the best for her.
所以她才被人绑架了
And this is why she was taken.
那现在怎么办
Shen, tell me what to do.
千万不要别接绑匪的电话
Don't take the kidnapper's calls.
你想她安全吗
Do you want your daughter back?
- 当然 - 照我说的做
- Of course. - Then do what I say.
那万一激怒他怎么办
But what if that provokes him?
难道不是应该顺着他们的要求吗
Aren't you always supposed to play to their demands?
时间拖的越长
The longer you delay talking to him…
机会就越大
the longer she lives.
记住我说的
Remember what I said.
沈
Shen…
直说 这地方有多糟糕
Straight up, how bad is this place?
很糟糕
It's bad.
这是个迷宫 雷
This place is a maze, Ray.
我从未见过这么令人生厌的地方
It's a hellhole like I've never seen.
听着 你撑我走了这么远 伙计
Look, you got me this far, man.
这不是你该打的仗
This is not your fight.
如果你想退出 我理解的
If you wanna pull out, I get it.
不 我挺你 伙计
No, I got your back, man.
我是来帮你的 我们一起
I'm here for you. Let's do it.
王
Wong.
怎么了
Yeah?
对不起
I'm sorry.
这不是你的错 振作点
It's not your fault. Stay positive.
王
Wong.
怎么了
Yeah?
我们一定会出去的
We'll get out of this together.
我们会的
We will.
你他妈的看什么 死筷子
What the fuck you looking at, chopsticks?
退后 桑尼 把门打开
Back up, Sonny. Open 'em up.
出来
Come on.
在所有人质中
Out of the hostages,
谁有你父亲公司里最高的安全许可
who has the highest security clearance in your father's company?
我知道你们都是天才
I know you're all geniuses,
你们都是最聪明 最优秀的
and I know you're all the best and the brightest.
但敏感问题上 他最信任谁
But who does he trust with sensitive matters?
我不知道
I don't know.
商业机密 谁他妈的有许可
Trade fucking secrets. Who has the clearance?
过来
Come here.
是这个人吗
Is it this guy?
是吗
Huh?
看啊 看啊
Look. Look, look.
不是吗 过来 过来
No? Come here. Come here.
那这家伙呢
What about this guy?
看看他
Look at him.
他有许可吗
Does he have the clearance?
告诉我 不然就开枪打爆他的头
Tell me, or I'll shoot him in the fucking head.
是我
It's me.
住手 是我
Stop. I do.
走啊 不要说话
No. Don't do it.
他会入侵公司
Once he has the information, he'll kill us.
等等 不要
Wait! No!
把她锁起来
Lock her up.
你要给我张氏的机密开发项目的权限
You're gonna give me access to Zhang's restricted developments.
让我们换一种方法试试
Uh… Let's try this a different way.
我要你教我怎么说中文
I want you to teach me how to speak Chinese.
你要教我怎么说
You're gonna teach me how to say,
「告诉我 不然我照脸来一枪」
"Tell me, or I will shoot you in the face."
用中文说
But in Chinese.
什么
What?
教我怎么说
Teach me how to say,
「告诉我 不然我照脸来一枪」 用中文
"Tell me, or I will shoot you in the face, " in Chinese.
有
There…
有一个五年投射计划
There is a five-year projection plan.
我要知道所有 你需要什么 笔记本
I want everything. What do you need, a laptop?
- 我 - 别说「不能」
- I… - Don't say "can't."
那是遗言
Those are last words.
我给他找台笔记本电脑
I'll get him a laptop.
哈什 你有什么进展
Hush, what have you got?
正在部署无人机
Deploying drone now.
你认为他们会把人质藏在哪里
Where do you think they're holding the hostages?
那家伙肯定是从监狱礼拜堂打来的
The guy definitely called from the prison chapel,
在这里
which is right there.
这里有东区 西区 行政区
You got the east block, west block, administration.
- 这地方有多大 - 超过1万8千平方米
- How big is this place? - Over 200, 000 square feet.
这些是什么壳
What kind of shells are those?
龙息 你知道是什么吗
Dragon's breath. You know what that is?
知道 计划把这个地方烧成平地吗
Yeah. Planning on burning this place to the ground?
是的 如果我们幸运的话
Yeah, if we're lucky.
听着 伙计们
Listen up, guys.
正在连接无人机图像
Uplinking drone feed now.
谢谢 哈什
Thanks, Hush.
好的 看到两个牢房区
Okay, we've got two cell blocks.
无人机热能正在显示 30
Uh, the thermal drone is showing… 30…
不 40 西区有40个人
No, 40. Forty bodies in the west block.
40什么 囚犯吗
40 what, prisoners?
看起来像 间隔均匀
It looks like it. They're spaced evenly.
天哪 他这是一个黑狱
Jesus Christ, he's running a black site.
好吧 还有什么 警卫呢
All right. What else, guards?
警卫塔 看起来有三个人
Guard tower. Looks like three people.
薄弱点呢 怎么进去 快点 朱勒
Weak spots. What's our way in? Come on, Jules.
屋顶上有两个热源点
There's two heat spots on the roof.
一个盖住了 另一个可能可以突破
One is covered, one might be accessible.
- 我可以上去 - 我不怀疑
- I can get up there. - I don't doubt that.
我们还在等什么
What are we waiting for?
- 我们不能盲跑 孩子 - 我们在浪费时间
- We don't run in blind, kid. - We're wasting time.
- 达雅是我负责的 - 闭嘴
- Daya is my responsibility. - Hey!
我也有朋友在里面
I got someone in there too.
从没见过有人开跑车去打架的
Never seen anyone go to a fight in a sports car before.
你要去哪儿
Hey, where you going.
你知道的 我更适合单独行动
You know me. I work better alone.
我或许会迟到一点
I may be late…
但我一定不会让你们失望的
…but I'll make a big impression.
祝你好运
Good luck.
莱斯
Les.
莱斯 你在干什么
Les, what are you doing?
你到底在干什么
What are you doing?
老兄 你得坚持下去啊
You gotta stay the course, man.
听着 我知道你想报仇
Look, I know you want revenge.
但是我们得先拿到那笔钱
but we gotta get that money.
你认识我父亲
You knew my father.
没错 他当时对我很好
He was good to me. Yeah.
但他现在已经不在人世了 而你还在
But he's all gone. You're still here.
我们必须得把钱搞到手
Let's get the money.
然后过上想过的生活
and live right.
咱他妈的能不管这贱货吗
Fuck this shit with that bitch.
好吧
Okay.
她在这儿会让人分心的
Well, she's a distraction.
我说 干脆咱直接杀了她就完事儿了
I say we kill her and be done with it.
弗兰基 就当是帮我个忙
Do me a favor, Frankie.
一切按我说的做 好吗
Just keep doing what I say, okay?
莱斯
Les.
我们必须杀了她
We gotta kill her.
就按我说的做
Do what I say!
你和莱斯的父亲之间是怎么回事
What's with you and Les's father?
你们曾是搭档 可他却出卖了你
You were his partner, and he sold you out.
为什么呢
Why?
为了五百万
Five million.
达雅的父亲也跟这事有关吗
And Daya's father's connected to this too?
全是父辈的恩怨啊
Lot of fathers here.
雷 你来看看这个
Hey, Ray, look at this.
你发现了什么
What do you got?
似乎浴室的戒备比较松懈
It looks like there might be a weak spot in the bathroom.
浴室的话
Bathroom.
连接着污水处理系统
The sewer system.
朱勒 你快看看
Jules, come on.
正在操作中
I'm on it.
（污水管道系统）
有管道平面图了
I got tunnels.
管道
Tunnels.
现在后悔还来得及
You have time.
你大可不必步入你父亲的旧尘
The sins of the father are not the sins of the son.
我们有客人来访了
We have visitors.
We got visitors.
请注意 我们有客人来访了
We got visitors!
已到达恶魔车站
Devil's Station.
- 报告目前状况 - 待命
- Status. - Standing by.
附近有敌人吗
See anybody?
暂无
Nothing yet.
这不可能啊
That can't be.
- 确实没人 - 检查过警卫塔没有
- That's all. - Check the guard towers?
检查了 没有人在那里
Yeah. No signs of life.
肯定有问题
Something's wrong.
此事必有蹊跷
This is very wrong.
- 伙计们 保持警惕 - 你也是
- Stay sharp, guys. Stay alert. - You too.
搞什么鬼 他知道我们来了
What the fuck. He knows we're coming.
他竟然知道我们的行踪
He knows we're coming.
你知道年兽的故事吗
You familiar with the legend of Nian?
是陷阱
Honeypot.
他们在拿达雅作诱饵
He's using Daya as bait.
你跟她之间到底有什么
What did you have with her?
你们在一起过吗
Were you together?
总之 我们现在要做的是必须等
We hold.
这是集体行动
This is a joint operation.
操
Shit.
年兽的故事是中国传说
It's… It's a Chinese legend.
没错 我想听听这个故事
Yeah. I wanna hear it.
快给我讲讲
Tell it to me.
古时候 有一只被称作年的怪兽
In ancient times, there was a monster called Nian.
每逢春天 年就会从巢穴里出来
Every spring, Nian would come out.
吃掉村民和家畜
and eat the villagers and livestock.
直到有一天 人们发现
And then one day, they discovered that…
烧竹子可以把年给吓走
burning bamboo scared the monster off.
通过竹子燃烧时发出的爆炸声 对吧
Made a crackling sound, didn't it?
没错
Yes.
所以 人们发明了爆竹来模拟这种声音
They invented firecrackers to re-create that sound.
我要把你留在这里
I'm gonna leave you out here…
然后再与里面的怪兽一战
fight the monster inside.
嘭 嘭 嘭
Pow, pow, pow.
你给我听着 我比你更想救达雅
Don't do that again. We work together for Daya.
那我们在等什么
Then what are we waiting for.
我们需要跟布雷斯林配合
We wait for Breslin.
我可不是为他干活儿的
I don't work for Breslin.
大伙儿们 表演时间到了 我们走
Showtime, everybody. Let's go!
你们知道该做些什么 立刻行动
You know what to do. Go now.
看看这个
Watch this.
武装完毕 随时待命
Armed and ready.
我警告你 你要再给我捣乱
You need to stop doing that.
我就不客
We wait for Breslin.
把他的手拴上
Zip him up.
我们走
Let's go.
好了
Okay.
谢谢你保镖先生
Thank you, Mr. Bodyguard.
我想让你做的事你都做了
You did exactly what I thought you'd do.
你带我找到了雷·布雷斯林
You led me to Ray Breslin.
还帮我抓到了他的女友
helped me capture his girl.
你们两个
Now, you two.
不仅浪费了时间 还浪费了生命
you both have wasted your time and your lives.
瞧瞧谁来了
Ah. Look who's here.
先生们 你们有两个选择 要么
Gentlemen, you have two choices. You can either…
你为什么老是盯着他看
Why are you staring at him?
- 我没有 - 你就是在看他
- I wasn't. - Yeah, you were.
- 我没有 - 你就是在直勾勾地看他
- No. - You were staring right at him.
你俩认识 对吧
You two know each other, don't you?
这其中肯定有蹊跷 我能感觉得到
Something's going on here. I can sense it. I sense something.
你为什么用那种眼神看我
Why do you look at me like that?
应该是你从我眼中看出仇恨
You gotta see this through my eyes.
我的父亲在船底闷死了
My father died boiling at the bottom of a ship.
如果当时 你们是让他坐在椅子上
I'd have had more respect if you sat him down in a chair,
在他面前揭露他的罪行
explained what he did wrong.
然后一枪崩了他 我心里还会好受一点
and then you put a bullet in his head.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
雷 你听到了吗
You hear that, Ray?
现在我的声音够大 够清楚了吗
Am I coming in loud and clear?
艾比
Abby.
雷 你将错过最精彩的环节
You're missing all the fun here, Ray.
伙计 你仔细听着 这是为你准备的
Keep listening, buddy. This is all for you.
他进地下通道了
He got in the tunnels.
把他的女友交给我处理
Leave Breslin's girl with me.
雷 我想给你看个东西
Hey, Ray, I want you to watch something.
看看你的手机
Have a look at your phone.
操
Fuck!
趴下
Fall down.
你给我起来
Get up!
进去
Go inside.
先生 你还是把电话接了吧
Sir, I suggest you answer the phone.
罗沈说了不要接
Shen said not to.
你这样做也无济于事啊
That's not how this works.
快接电话
Answer the phone!
你爸不肯接电话
Your father won't answer the phone.
布雷斯林搞的鬼
Breslin.
你们闻到烟味了吗
Hey! Hey, you smell that?
快拉警报
Sound the alarm!
闭嘴 快闭上你们的臭嘴
Shut up! Hey, shut up! Shut your fucking mouths!
都给我闭嘴
Shut up!
- 快点 - 回牢房去
- Come on! - Move! Move back!
举起手来
Let me see your hands!
不许动
Don't move!
给老子趴下
Get the fuck down!
- 举起手来 - 快他妈的趴下
- Give me your hands! - Get the fuck down!
趴下
Get down!
前面的人快趴下
Down in front!
快跑
Go!
快走
布雷斯林到附近了
Breslin's in the near.
妈的
Shit.
你说什么
What?
布雷斯林就在附近
Breslin is nearby.
你负责镇压住犯人
Take care of the prisoners.
你他妈去把那用电脑的小鬼带过来
Bring me that fuckin' kid on the computer.
布雷斯林由我来对付
I'll take care of Breslin.
好吧
All right.
王 我们得找到王
Wong. We need to find Wong.
你黑进去了没有
Did you hack in?
来啊
Come on!
我们走
Let's go.
你为什么要杀她
Why'd you kill her?
谁让她跟你在一起
Being with you killed her.
这就是我的报复
This is payback.
值得吗
Was it worth it?
你老爸恨死你了
Your old man hated you!
雷 你他妈的满嘴屁话
Ah, you're full of shit, Ray!
你知道吗 雷
Know what, Ray?
她都没有尖叫
She didn't even scream.
充其量就是咕哝了两声
Kinda just gurgled.
你这么做是为了你父亲吗
You did this for your father?
你爱你父亲吗 你爱你父亲吗
You loved your father? You loved your father?
来呀 打我呀 替你爸打我
Come on. Hit me. Hit me for your father.
你要我来 我来了 动手啊
You wanted me, you got me. Come on.
你他妈的没吃饭吗
You call that a fuckin' hit?
- 你个弱鸡 - 等等 等等
- You fuckin' pussy. - Wait, wait.
我会杀了你的 我来跟你说说我爸
I'll fuckin' kill you. Let me tell you about my father.
我来告诉你我爸是个什么样的人
Let me tell you about my fuckin' father.
起来
Get up.
很好 我告诉你我爸是个什么样的人
That's right. Let me tell you about my father.
真的吗
Really?
他是这个世界上最恶毒的老王八蛋
He was the meanest son of a bitch in the world.
你知道他跟我说过什么吗 你知道吗
Know what he said? Know what he said?
你知道他怎么说我吗 他说
You know what he said? He said,
儿子 你要学着宽恕
"You should learn to forgive, son.
不该这么恶毒
You shouldn't be so mean."
我说 你说得太晚了
I said, "You know, it's too late.
你已经造就了现在的我
You made me what I am."
什么都别说
Don't say anything. Shh.
什么都别说了
Don't say anything.
等一下 等一下
Wait, wait.
这就是
This is what it…
这就是我当时的感受
This is what it felt like.
你痛失所爱 我深表遗憾
Please accept my sympathy for your loss.
别说话
No.
还记得沈吗
Remember Shen?
他会送我回家
He will be taking me home.
你不介意吧
You don't mind, do you?
介意啊 真的挺麻烦的
Well, I had other plans,
不过是为了你
but for you I'll break them.
我会负责阿比盖尔的
I'll take care of Abigail's arrival arrangements.
那就多谢了
Appreciate it.
- 有件事要你去做 - 什么
- There's something you gotta do. - What?
你要原谅你自己 不是你的错
You gotta forgive yourself. Wasn't your fault.
不容易办到啊
Not gonna be so easy to do.
我他妈受够监狱了
I'm done with prisons.
- 不去监狱了 - 再也不去了
- No more prisons? - No more.
那我可太开心了 接下来有什么打算
That's music to me. Any ideas?
怎么都行 只要在外面就行
Anything outside sounds good.
外面对你的身体有好处
Outside is good for your health.
我们好好想想
Let's talk about this.
你有什么想法吗
You got any ideas?
南美怎么样
What do you think about South America?
有点远
It's kinda far away.
先别忙着拒绝 你欠我的 记得吗
Before you say no, remember, you owe me.
我在那边有个认识的人
I know this guy down there.
他名声有点不好 不过我跟你说
He's a little shady, but I'm telling you…
有点不好而已吗
A little?
我们认识的人就没有名声好的
Everyone we know is shady.
∮ 我已不能直视 ∮
∮ I can't stare down ∮
∮ 枪口喷出的火焰 ∮
∮ The barrel of a gun again ∮
∮ 亦不知如何 ∮
∮ I don't know how ∮
∮ 再重展笑颜 ∮
∮ I'm gonna have fun again ∮
∮ 这一切像是 ∮
∮ And this feels like ∮
∮ 虎口脱险 ∮
∮ I'm running from a lion ∮
∮ 又更像是 是身陷烈焰 ∮
∮ No, this feels like I'm burning in a fire ∮
∮ 继续坚守吧 今夜无人生还 ∮
∮ Hold on tight Someone's gonna die tonight ∮
∮ 逃离 ∮
∮ Get out ∮
∮ 这令人窒息的水面 ∮
∮ Get up out of the water ∮
∮ 逃吧 ∮
∮ Get out ∮
∮ 否则你将倒在我的枪口面前 ∮
∮ Before I shoot you down ∮
∮ 一切归于这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ It's down to playing games Wicked games ∮
∮ 这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ Playing wicked games ∮
∮ 一切归于这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ Down to playing games Wicked games ∮
∮ 这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ Playing wicked games ∮
∮ 逃离 ∮
∮ Get out ∮
∮ 这令人窒息的水面 ∮
∮ Get up out of the water ∮
∮ 否则你将倒在我的枪口面前 ∮
∮ Before I shoot you down ∮
∮ 倒在 我的 面前 ∮
∮ Down, d-d-down ∮
∮ Down, down, down D-D-Down ∮
∮ 寒冷沁入骨髓 ∮
∮ Just so cold ∮
∮ 因我踏进这地狱无间 ∮
∮ Step into the battle zone ∮
∮ 千金之注 ∮
∮ There's a weight of gold ∮
∮ 押在这终局之间 ∮
∮ Ridin' on the final blow ∮
∮ 你无法逃脱 ∮
∮ I'll chase you down ∮
∮ 我如蛆附骨的追击 ∮
∮ Hunt you like an animal ∮
∮ 不知停息 至你终成钢筋铁骨 ∮
∮ Round and round Until you're made of metal ∮
∮ 继续坚守吧 今夜无人生还 ∮
∮ Hold on tight Someone's gonna die tonight ∮
∮ 无人生还 无人生还 无人生还 ∮
∮ Die tonight, die tonight Die tonight, die tonight ∮
∮ 逃离 ∮
∮ Get out ∮
∮ 这令人窒息的水面 ∮
∮ Get up out of the water ∮
∮ 逃吧 ∮
∮ Get out ∮
∮ 否则你将倒在我的枪口面前 ∮
∮ Before I shoot you down ∮
∮ 一切归于这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ It's down to playing games Wicked games ∮
∮ 这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ Playing wicked games ∮
∮ 归于这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ Down to playing games Wicked games ∮
∮ 这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ Playing wicked games ∮
∮ 逃离 ∮
∮ Get out ∮
∮ 这令人窒息的水面 ∮
∮ Get up out of the water ∮
∮ 否则你将倒在我的枪口面前 ∮
∮ Before I shoot you down ∮
∮ 倒在 我的 面前 ∮
∮ Down, d-d-down ∮
∮ Down, down, down D-D-Down ∮
∮ 倒在 我的 面前 ∮
∮ Down, down, d-d-down ∮
∮ Down, down, down D-D-Down ∮
∮ 倒在 我的 面前 ∮
∮ Down, down, d-d-down ∮
∮ Down, down, down D-D-Down ∮
∮ 倒在 我的 面前 ∮
∮ Down, down, d-d-down ∮
∮ Down, down, down D-D-Down ∮
∮ 你让我知道置身高处的感觉 ∮
∮ Now you got me high As high as I've been ∮
∮ 今夜 送我到死神面前 ∮
∮ Come shoot me down tonight ∮
《金蝉脱壳3：恶魔车站》
∮ 逃吧 ∮
∮ Get out ∮
∮ 否则你将倒在我的枪口面前 ∮
∮ Before I shoot you down ∮
∮ 一切归于这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ It's down to playing games Wicked games ∮
∮ 这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ Playing wicked games ∮
∮ 归于这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ Down to playing games Wicked games ∮
∮ 这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ Playing wicked games ∮
∮ 逃离 ∮
∮ Get out ∮
∮ 这令人窒息的水面 ∮
∮ Get up out of the water ∮
∮ 否则你将倒在我的枪口面前 ∮
∮ Before I shoot you down ∮
∮ 倒在 我的 面前 ∮
∮ Down, d-d-down ∮
∮ Down, down, down D-D-Down ∮
∮ 倒在 我的 面前 ∮
∮ Down, down, d-d-down ∮
∮ Down, down, down D-D-Down ∮
∮ 我身在 ∮
∮ You got me right ∮
∮ 你的股掌之间 ∮
∮ Right in between your fingers ∮
∮ 却甘之如饴 ∮
∮ I'm all right ∮
∮ 你让我知道置身高处的感觉 ∮
∮ Yeah, you got me high As high as I've been ∮
∮ 今夜 送我到死神面前 ∮
∮ Come shoot me down tonight ∮
∮ 逃离 ∮
∮ Get out ∮
∮ 这令人窒息的水面 ∮
∮ Get up out of the water ∮
∮ 逃吧 ∮
∮ Get out ∮
∮ 否则你将倒在我的枪口面前 ∮
∮ Before I shoot you down ∮
∮ 一切归于这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ It's down to playing games Wicked games ∮
∮ 这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ Playing wicked games ∮
∮ 归于这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ Down to playing games Wicked games ∮
∮ 这邪恶的游戏 ∮
∮ Playing wicked games ∮
∮ 逃离 ∮
∮ Get out ∮
∮ 这令人窒息的水面 ∮
∮ Get up out of the water ∮
∮ 否则你将倒在我的枪口面前 ∮
∮ Before I shoot you down ∮
∮ 倒在 我的 面前 ∮
∮ Down, d-d-down ∮
∮ Down, down, down D-D-Down ∮
∮ 倒在 我的 面前 ∮
∮ Down, down, d-d-down ∮
∮ Down, down, down D-D-Down ∮
∮ 倒在 我的 面前 ∮
∮ Down, down, d-d-down ∮
∮ Down, down, down D-D-Down ∮
∮ 倒在 我的 面前 ∮
∮ Down, down, d-d-down ∮
∮ Down, down, down D-D-Down ∮